[
  {
    "test_id": 8,
    "q_no": 1,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Fill in the blanks",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 1,
    "question": "Question 1",
    "your_ans": "my ans 1",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher ans 1"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 8,
    "q_no": 2,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Fill in the blanks",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 1,
    "question": "History Question 2",
    "your_ans": "my History ans 2",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher History ans 2"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 8,
    "q_no": 3,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Explain in brief",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 0,
    "question": "History Question 3",
    "your_ans": "my History ans 3",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher History ans 3"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 8,
    "q_no": 4,
    "topic_id": 2,
    "topic_name": "Explain in Brief",
    "topic_marks": 5,
    "given_marks": 3,
    "question": "History Question 4",
    "your_ans": "my History ans 4",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher History ans 4"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 9,
    "q_no": 1,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Fill in the blanks",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 0,
    "question": "Kannada Question 1",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 1",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 1"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 9,
    "q_no": 2,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Fill in the blanks",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 1,
    "question": "Kannada Question 2",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 2",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 2"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 9,
    "q_no": 3,
    "topic_id": 2,
    "topic_name": "Explain in Brief",
    "topic_marks": 5,
    "given_marks": 4,
    "question": "Kannada Question 3",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 3",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 3"
  },
 {
    "test_id": 9,
    "q_no": 4,
    "topic_id": 2,
    "topic_name": "Explain in Brief",
    "topic_marks": 5,
    "given_marks": 5,
    "question": "Kannada Question 4",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 4",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 4"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 10,
    "q_no": 1,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Fill in the blanks",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 0,
    "question": "Kannada Question 1",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 1",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 1"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 10,
    "q_no": 2,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Fill in the blanks",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 1,
    "question": "Kannada Question 2",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 2",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 2"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 10,
    "q_no": 3,
    "topic_id": 2,
    "topic_name": "Explain in Brief",
    "topic_marks": 5,
    "given_marks": 4,
    "question": "Kannada Question 3",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 3",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 3"
  },
 {
    "test_id": 10,
    "q_no": 4,
    "topic_id": 2,
    "topic_name": "Explain in Brief",
    "topic_marks": 5,
    "given_marks": 5,
    "question": "Kannada Question 4",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 4",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 4"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 11,
    "q_no": 1,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Fill in the blanks",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 0,
    "question": "Kannada Question 1",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 1",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 1"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 11,
    "q_no": 2,
    "topic_id": 1,
    "topic_name": "Fill in the blanks",
    "topic_marks": 1,
    "given_marks": 1,
    "question": "Kannada Question 2",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 2",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 2"
  },
  {
    "test_id": 11,
    "q_no": 3,
    "topic_id": 2,
    "topic_name": "Explain in Brief",
    "topic_marks": 5,
    "given_marks": 4,
    "question": "Kannada Question 3",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 3",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 3"
  },
 {
    "test_id": 11,
    "q_no": 4,
    "topic_id": 2,
    "topic_name": "Explain in Brief",
    "topic_marks": 5,
    "given_marks": 5,
    "question": "Kannada Question 4",
    "your_ans": "my Kannada ans 4",
    "teacher_ans": "teacher Kannada ans 4"
  }
]